mixpod.com 2010-06-26

# Privacy Policy - MixPod.com

Your privacy is important to us and as described in this Privacy Policy, we have designed the Service to protect information about you from unauthorized disclosure to others. We do not sell or rent your personally identifying information to any third party. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and, in certain circumstances, share your personal identifying information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and if you have any questions, feel free to contact us. 

By using the Service, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. From time to time, we may update the Privacy Policy and we will post a notice of significant changes on the website www.MixPod.com. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the Privacy Policy. 

####  What We Collect

When you register to become a member of MixPod, we collect your email address and other personal identifying information that you submit. 

####  How We Use Your Information

We use your name, email address and other information on our system to notify you of new product releases, service notifications, and to solicit your feedback and input. 

You understand and agree that we may access, preserve, and the contents of your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to avoid liability, to comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect our rights and property, or that of our affiliates or the public. MixPod may also delete certain content in whole or in part if MixPod determines, in its sole discretion, that such content constitutes an .Infringing Posting. or a .Prohibited Posting. 

We also use non-personally identifiable information and certain technical information about your computer in order to operate, maintain and manage the Service. 

####  Controlling Your Personal Information

You can terminate your account at any time which will remove your account. MixPod, however, may (but is not obligated to) keep information about you that is on its system following your termination. Contact MixPod to terminate your account or for any other questions about your personal information. 

#### Transfer of Information

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of MixPod, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, MixPod will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

####  Links to Other Sites

MixPod may contain links to other web sites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information. It is up to you to review those policies yourself. 

####  Security

We use industry standard security measures to protect your information so that it is not made available to unauthorized parties. If you have any questions regarding which measures and techniques we use, feel free to contact us.
